const nfpa211Chapter3QuizData = [
  {
    id: "3_1",
    question: "'Approved' means it is acceptable to the ____________. (NFPA 211 3.2.1)",
    options: ["Homeowner", "Company", "Authority Having Jurisdiction", "Manufacturer"],
    answer: "Authority Having Jurisdiction"
  },
  {
    id: "3_2",
    question: "__________ : An organization, office, or individual responsible for enforcing the requirements of a code or standard, or for approving equipment, materials and installation, or a procedure. (NFPA 211 3.2.2)",
    options: ["Manager/Lead", "IRC", "Authority Having Jurisdiction", "Qualified Agency"],
    answer: "Authority Having Jurisdiction"
  },
  {
    id: "3_3",
    question: "__________ : Equipment or materials to which has been attached a label, symbol, or other identifying mark of an organization that is acceptable to the authority having jurisdiction and concerned with product evaluation, that maintains periodic inspection of production of labeled equipment or materials, and by whose labeling the manufacturer indicates compliance with appropriate standards or performance in a specified manner. (NFPA 211 3.2.3)",
    options: ["Identified", "Labeled", "Listed", "Approved"],
    answer: "Labeled"
  },
  {
    id: "3_4",
    question: "__________ : Equipment, materials, or services included in a list published by an organization that is acceptable to the authority having jurisdiction and concerned with evaluation of products or services, that maintains periodic inspection of production of listed equipment or materials or periodic evaluation of services, and whose listing states that either the equipment, material, or service meets appropriate designated standards or has been tested and found suitable for a specified purpose. (NFPA 211 3.2.4)",
    options: ["Labeled", "Listed", "Published", "Approved"],
    answer: "Listed"
  },
  {
    id: "3_5",
    question: "__________ : Indicates a mandatory requirement. (NFPA 211 3.2.5)",
    options: ["Approved", "Shall", "Should", "Recommended"],
    answer: "Shall"
  },
  {
    id: "3_6",
    question: "__________ : Indicates a recommendation or that which is advised but not required. (NFPA 211 3.2.6)",
    options: ["Approved", "Shall", "Should", "Mandatory"],
    answer: "Should"
  },
  {
    id: "3_7",
    question: "__________ : An NFPA standard, the main text of which contains only mandatory provisions using the word 'shall' to indicate requirements and that is in a form generally suitable for mandatory reference by another standard or code or for adoption into law. Non mandatory provisions are not to be considered a part of the requirements of a standard and shall be located in appendix, annex, footnote, informational note, or other means as permitted in the NFPA manuals of style. When used in a generic sense, such as in the phrases 'standards development process' or 'standards development activities,' the term 'standards' includes all NFPA standards, including codes, standards, recommended practices, and guides. (NFPA 211 3.2.7)",
    options: ["Code", "Standard", "Recommendations", "Requirements"],
    answer: "Standard"
  },
  {
    id: "3_8",
    question: "__________ : Capable of being exposed for inspection, maintenance, or repair without damage to the chimney or building structure of finish, but which might require the removal of doors, panels, or coverings using commonly available tools. (NFPA 211 3.3.1)",
    options: ["Readily Accessible", "Accessible", "Concealed (Inaccessible)", "Available"],
    answer: "Accessible"
  },
  {
    id: "3_9",
    question: "__________ : Exposed, or capable of being exposed, for operation, inspection, maintenance, or repair without the use of tools to open or remove doors, panels, or coverings. (NFPA 211 3.3.1.1)",
    options: ["Readily Accessible", "Accessible", "Inaccessible", "Available"],
    answer: "Readily Accessible"
  },
  {
    id: "3_10",
    question: "__________ : Supplementary part or device added to an appliance to make it more useful, versatile, attractive and so forth. (NFPA 211 3.3.2)",
    options: ["Assistor", "Accessory", "Enhancement", "Appliance Sidekick"],
    answer: "Accessory"
  },
  {
    id: "3_11",
    question: "Factory-Built Fireplace Accessories : Accessories intended for field installation into or attachment to factory-built and masonry fireplaces. (NFPA 211 3.3.2.1)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "False"
  },
  {
    id: "3_12",
    question: "Masonry Fireplace Accessories : Accessories intended for field installation into or attachment to masonry fireplaces. (NFPA 211 3.3.2.2)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True"
  },
  {
    id: "3_13",
    question: "__________ : The air necessary to provide for the complete combustion of fuel and usually consisting of primary air, secondary air, and excess air. (NFPA 211 3.3.3.1)",
    options: ["Flue Gases", "Combustion Air", "Carbon Monoxide", "Draft"],
    answer: "Combustion Air"
  },
  {
    id: "3_14",
    question: "__________ : Any device that utilizes a fuel to produce light, heat, power, refrigeration, or air conditioning. (NFPA 211 3.3.4)",
    options: ["Fireplace", "Accessory", "Vent", "Appliance"],
    answer: "Appliance"
  },
  {
    id: "3_15",
    question: "__________ : Appliances such as gas-operated coffee brewers and coffee urns and any appurtenant water-heating equipment, food and dish warmers, hot plates and griddles. (NFPA 211 3.3.4.1)",
    options: ["Direct Vent Appliance", "Building Heat Appliance", "Counter Appliance (Gas)", "Fuel-Burning Appliance"],
    answer: "Counter Appliance (Gas)"
  },
  {
    id: "3_16",
    question: "__________ : A system consisting of an appliance, combustion air and flue gas connections between the appliance and the outside atmosphere, and a vent cap supplied by the manufacturer, and constructed so that all air for combustion is obtained from the outside atmosphere and all flue gases are discharged to the outside atmosphere. (NFPA 211 3.3.4.2)",
    options: ["Direct Vent Appliance", "Barometric Draft Regulator", "Counter Appliance (Gas)", "Automatic Electric Igniter"],
    answer: "Direct Vent Appliance"
  },
  {
    id: "3_17",
    question: "__________ : A closed combustion pellet vent or chimney-connected solid pellet fuel-burning appliance incorporating a fuel-feed control mechanism. (NFPA 211 3.3.4.3.1)",
    options: ["Factory-Built Fireplace", "Boiler", "Gas Insert", "Pellet Fuel-Burning Appliance"],
    answer: "Pellet Fuel-Burning Appliance"
  },
  {
    id: "3_18",
    question: "__________ : A chimney-connected device that burns solid fuel designed for purposes of heating, cooking, or both. (NFPA 211 3.3.4.3.2)",
    options: ["Solid Fuel-Burning Appliance", "Vented Appliance", "Counter Appliance (Gas)", "Pellet Fuel-Burning Appliance"],
    answer: "Solid Fuel-Burning Appliance"
  },
  {
    id: "3_19",
    question: "__________ : A heating appliance designed specifically for installation in an attic or in a space with low headroom that normally is unoccupied. (NFPA 211 3.3.4.4.1)",
    options: ["Nonresidential, Medium-Heat Appliance", "Attic-Type Heating Appliance", "Free Standing Wood Stove", "Wood Burning Insert"],
    answer: "Attic-Type Heating Appliance"
  },
  {
    id: "3_20",
    question: "A Building Heating Appliance is a Nonresidential, Low-Heat Appliance. (NFPA 211 3.3.4.4.2)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True"
  },
  {
    id: "3_21",
    question: "__________ : Fuel-Burning appliances, not including high-pressure steam boilers, that are mainly used in residences but that might be used in other buildings and that do not produce continuous flue gas temperatures exceeding 1000°F. (NFPA 211 3.3.4.4.3)",
    options: ["Counter Appliance", "Residential-Type Heating Appliance", "Nonresidential, High-Heat Appliance", "Nonresidential, Medium-Heat-Appliance"],
    answer: "Residential-Type Heating Appliance"
  },
  {
    id: "3_22",
    question: "Residential-Type Heating Appliances are meant for appliances that do not produce continuous flue gas temperatures exceeding 800°F. (NFPA 211 3.3.4.4.3)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "False"
  },
  {
    id: "3_23",
    question: "Heat-Producing Appliances produce heat by utilizing electric energy OR by burning fuel. (NFPA 211 3.3.4.5)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True"
  },
  {
    id: "3_24",
    question: "__________ : A commercial, industrial, or institutional appliance needing a chimney capable of withstanding a continuous flue gas temperature not exceeding 1400°F. (NFPA 211 3.3.4.6)",
    options: ["Nonresidential, Low-Heat Appliance", "Nonresidential Appliance, 1400°F", "Nonresidential, High-Heat Appliance", "Nonresidential, Medium-Heat Appliance"],
    answer: "Nonresidential Appliance, 1400°F"
  },
  {
    id: "3_25",
    question: "__________ : A commercial, industrial, or institutional appliance needing a chimney capable of withstanding a continuous flue gas temperature exceeding 1800°F. (NFPA 211 3.3.4.7)",
    options: ["Nonresidential, Low-Heat Appliance", "Nonresidential Appliance, 1400°F", "Nonresidential, High-Heat Appliance", "Nonresidential, Medium-Heat Appliance"],
    answer: "Nonresidential, High-Heat Appliance"
  },
  {
    id: "3_26",
    question: "__________ : A commercial, industrial, or institutional appliance needing a chimney capable of withstanding a continuous flue gas temperature not exceeding 1000°F. (NFPA 211 3.3.4.8)",
    options: ["Nonresidential, Low-Heat Appliance", "Nonresidential Appliance, 1400°F", "Nonresidential, High-Heat Appliance", "Nonresidential, Medium-Heat Appliance"],
    answer: "Nonresidential, Low-Heat Appliance"
  },
  {
    id: "3_27",
    question: "__________ : A commercial, industrial, or institutional appliance needing a chimney capable of withstanding a continuous flue gas temperature not exceeding 1800°F. (NFPA 211 3.3.4.9)",
    options: ["Nonresidential, Low-Heat Appliance", "Nonresidential Appliance, 1400°F", "Nonresidential, High-Heat Appliance", "Nonresidential, Medium-Heat Appliance"],
    answer: "Nonresidential, Medium-Heat Appliance"
  },
  {
    id: "3_28",
    question: "__________ : An indirect-fired appliance provided with a flue collar to accommodate a venting system for conveying flue gases to the outside atmosphere. (NFPA 211 3.3.4.10)",
    options: ["Automatic Electric Igniter", "Open Masonry Fireplace", "Vented Appliance", "Factory-Built Chimney"],
    answer: "Vented Appliance"
  },
  {
    id: "3_29",
    question: "__________ : An enclosure forming the outside of the appliance. (NFPA 211 3.3.5)",
    options: ["Chase", "Liner", "Appliance Casing (or Jacket)", "Baffle Plate"],
    answer: "Appliance Casing (or Jacket)"
  },
  {
    id: "3_30",
    question: "__________ : The solid residue that remains after combustion is complete. (NFPA 211 3.3.8)",
    options: ["Ash", "Wood", "Creosote", "Baffle"],
    answer: "Ash"
  },
  {
    id: "3_31",
    question: "__________ : A door below the grade level providing access to the ash receptacle. (NFPA 211 3.3.9)",
    options: ["Ash Receptacle Door", "Wash", "Vent", "Flue"],
    answer: "Ash Receptacle Door"
  },
  {
    id: "3_32",
    question: "__________ : A device for fuel burners designed to utilize electric energy for ignition of a fuel-air mixture at the burner. (NFPA 211 3.3.11)",
    options: ["Boiler", "Automatic Electric Igniter", "Combustion", "Dilution Flue"],
    answer: "Automatic Electric Igniter"
  },
  {
    id: "3_33",
    question: "__________ : A device built into a fuel-burning appliance, or made a part of a chimney connector or vent connector, that functions to reduce excessive draft through an appliance to a desired value by admitting ambient air into the appliance chimney, chimney connector, vent, or vent connector. (NFPA 211 3.3.13)",
    options: ["Damper", "Thimble", "Baffle", "Barometric Draft Regulator"],
    answer: "Barometric Draft Regulator"
  },
  {
    id: "3_34",
    question: "__________ : A closed vessel in which water is heated, steam is generated, steam is superheated, or any combination thereof by the application of heat from combustible fuels in a self-contained or attached furnace. (NFPA 211 3.3.14)",
    options: ["Free Standing Wood Stove", "Gas Insert", "Boiler", "Duct Furnace"],
    answer: "Boiler"
  },
  {
    id: "3_35",
    question: "__________ : A single boiler unit designed to burn more than one type of fuel (gas, oil, solid), either separately or simultaneously, using either separate or common combustion chambers and flues. (NFPA 211 3.3.14.1)",
    options: ["Supplementary Boiler", "Combination-Fuel Boiler", "Central Warm-Air Furnace", "Central Warm-Air, Gravity-Type Furnace"],
    answer: "Combination-Fuel Boiler"
  },
  {
    id: "3_36",
    question: "__________ : A boiler for generating steam at gauge pressures in excess of 15 psi, or for heating water to a temperature in excess of 250°F or at a gauge pressure in excess of 160 psi.. (NFPA 211 3.3.14.2)",
    options: ["Supplementary Boiler", "Combination-Fuel Boiler", "High-Pressure Boiler", "Low-Pressure Boiler"],
    answer: "High-Pressure Boiler"
  },
  {
    id: "3_37",
    question: "__________ : A boiler for generating steam at gauge pressures not in excess of 15 psi, or for furnishing water at a maximum temperature of 250°F at a maximum gauge pressure of 160 psi. (NFPA 211 3.3.14.3)",
    options: ["Supplementary Boiler", "Combination-Fuel Boiler", "High-Pressure Boiler", "Low-Pressure Boiler"],
    answer: "Low-Pressure Boiler"
  },
  {
    id: "3_38",
    question: "__________ : A boiler, designed to burn one type of fuel (gas, oil, or solid), that is intended for supplementing a boiler burning another type of fuel (gas, oil, or solid) by means of a common heat transfer medium. (NFPA 211 3.3.14.4)",
    options: ["Supplementary Boiler", "Combination-Fuel Boiler", "Central Warm-Air Furnace", "Central Warm-Air, Gravity-Type Furnace"],
    answer: "Supplementary Boiler"
  },
  {
    id: "3_39",
    question: "__________ : Where referring to bricklaying and masonry chimneys, that connection between brick, stone, or other masonry units formed by lapping them upon one another in carrying up the work, thereby forming an inseparable mass. (NFPA 211 3.3.15)",
    options: ["Join", "Bond", "Point of Contact", "Corbel"],
    answer: "Bond"
  },
  {
    id: "3_40",
    question: "__________ : The conduit conveying flue gas from the appliance to the chimney. (NFPA 211 3.3.16)",
    options: ["Breeching", "Flue", "Flue Collar", "Draft Hood"],
    answer: "Breeching"
  },
  {
    id: "3_41",
    question: "__________ : The quantity of heat needed to raise the temperature of 1 pound of water 1°F. (NFPA 211 3.3.17)",
    options: ["BTU", "Force", "Thermal", "Temperature"],
    answer: "BTU"
  },
  {
    id: "3_42",
    question: "What does BTU stand for? (NFPA 211 3.3.17)",
    options: ["British Technical Understanding", "Belgium Thermal Unit", "British Thermal Unit", "Brazilian Thermal Underlayment"],
    answer: "British Thermal Unit"
  },
  {
    id: "3_43",
    question: "__________ : A protective covering or housing for the top of a chimney intended to prevent the entry of rain, snow, animals, and birds, and to prevent downdrafts. (NFPA 211 3.3.19.1)",
    options: ["Vent Cap", "Draft Hood", "Chimney Cap", "Spark Arrestor"],
    answer: "Chimney Cap"
  },
  {
    id: "3_44",
    question: "__________ : A protective covering or housing attached to the vent termination, intended for preventing downdrafts and the entry of rain, snow, and animals. (NFPA 211 3.3.19.2)",
    options: ["Vent Cap", "Draft Hood", "Chimney Cap", "Spark Arrestor"],
    answer: "Vent Cap"
  },
  {
    id: "3_45",
    question: "__________ : A structure containing one or more vertical or nearly vertical passageways for conveying flue gases to the outside atmosphere. (NFPA 211 3.3.29)",
    options: ["Flue", "Connector Pipe", "Chimney", "Heat Reclaimer"],
    answer: "Chimney"
  },
  {
    id: "3_46",
    question: "__________ : A heating appliance chimney suitable for continuous use at 1000°F, composed of listed, factory-built components, designed for open, non-enclosed use at specified minimum clearances to combustibles, and assembled in accordance with the terms of the listing to form the completed chimney. (NFPA 211 3.3.29.1.1)",
    options: ["Factory-Built, Building Heating Appliance-Type Chimney", "Factory-Built 1400°F F-Type Chimney", "Masonry Chimney", "Factory-Built, Medium-Heat Appliance-Type Chimney"],
    answer: "Factory-Built, Building Heating Appliance-Type Chimney"
  },
  {
    id: "3_47",
    question: "__________ : A chimney suitable for use at 1000°F, which complies with the 10 minute 1700°F temperature test of UL 103, and is composed of listed, factory-built components that might be fully enclosed in combustible, residential-type construction, and that is assembled in accordance with the terms of the listing to form a completed chimney. (NFPA 211 3.3.29.1.2)",
    options: ["Factory-Built, Building Heating Appliance-Type Chimney", "Factory-Built 1400°F F-Type Chimney", "Factory-Built, Residential-Type and Building Heating Appliance-Type Chimney", "Factory-Built, Medium-Heat Appliance-Type Chimney"],
    answer: "Factory-Built, Residential-Type and Building Heating Appliance-Type Chimney"
  },
  {
    id: "3_48",
    question: "__________ : A residential type and building heating appliance chimney suitable for use at 1000°F, which complies with the optional 10 minute 2100°F temperature test of UL 103. Such chimneys are labeled as type HT and are required for certain solid fuel-fired applications. (NFPA 211 3.3.29.1.3)",
    options: ["Type HT Factory-Built, Residential-Type and/or Building Heating Appliance-Type Chimney", "Factory-Built 1400°F F-Type Chimney", "Factory-Built, Residential-Type and Building Heating Appliance-Type Chimney", "Factory-Built, Medium-Heat Appliance-Type Chimney"],
    answer: "Type HT Factory-Built, Residential-Type and/or Building Heating Appliance-Type Chimney"
  },
  {
    id: "3_49",
    question: "__________ : A chimney suitable for continuous use at 1400°F, composed of listed, factory-built components, intended for open, non-enclosed use at specified minimum clearances to combustibles and for use in noncombustible locations, and assembled in accordance with the terms of the listing to form the completed chimney. (NFPA 211 3.3.29.2)",
    options: ["Type HT Factory-Built, Residential-Type and/or Building Heating Appliance-Type Chimney", "Factory-Built 1400°F F-Type Chimney", "Factory-Built, Residential-Type and Building Heating Appliance-Type Chimney", "Factory-Built, Medium-Heat Appliance-Type Chimney"],
    answer: "Factory-Built 1400°F F-Type Chimney"
  },
  {
    id: "3_50",
    question: "__________ : A chimney used with appliances that produce maximum flue gas temperatures of 1800°F, composed of listed, factory-built components, suitable for open, non-enclosed use at specified minimum clearances to combustibles, and assembled in accordance with the terms of the listing to form the completed chimney. (NFPA 211 3.3.29.3)",
    options: ["Type HT Factory-Built, Residential-Type and/or Building Heating Appliance-Type Chimney", "Factory-Built 1400°F F-Type Chimney", "Factory-Built, Residential-Type and Building Heating Appliance-Type Chimney", "Factory-Built, Medium-Heat Appliance-Type Chimney"],
    answer: "Factory-Built, Medium-Heat Appliance-Type Chimney"
  },
  {
    id: "3_51",
    question: "__________ : A residential-type or building heating appliance chimney, or both, listed for use in positive internal pressure applications. (NFPA 211 3.3.29.4)",
    options: ["Factory-Built, Positive Pressure Capable Chimney", "Factory-Built, Negative Pressure Capable Chimney", "Low-Pressure Boiler", "Masonry Chimney"],
    answer: "Factory-Built, Positive Pressure Capable Chimney"
  },
  {
    id: "3_52",
    question: "__________ : A field-constructed chimney of solid masonry units, bricks, stones, listed masonry chimney units, or reinforced Portland cement concrete, lined with suitable chimney flue liners. (NFPA 211 3.3.29.5)",
    options: ["Factory-Built, Positive Pressure Capable Chimney", "Factory-Built, Negative Pressure Capable Chimney", "Masonry Chimney", "Unlisted Metal Chimney"],
    answer: "Masonry Chimney"
  },
  {
    id: "3_53",
    question: "__________ : A manufactured or field-constructed chimney intended only for nonresidential applications having one or more metal walls, or made of metal with a refractory lining, and that is capable of withstanding the flue gas conditions of its use. (NFPA 211 3.3.29.6)",
    options: ["Factory-Built, Positive Pressure Capable Chimney", "Factory-Built, Negative Pressure Capable Chimney", "Masonry Chimney", "Unlisted Metal (Smokestack) Chimney"],
    answer: "Unlisted Metal (Smokestack) Chimney"
  },
  {
    id: "3_54",
    question: "__________ : A heat exchanger intended to be installed in a chimney connector between a heating appliance and the chimney to transfer heat from the flue gases through metal to air or water. (NFPA 211 3.3.32)",
    options: ["Chimney Connector-Type Heat Reclaimer", "Dilution Flue", "Damper", "Radiant Room Heater"],
    answer: "Chimney Connector-Type Heat Reclaimer"
  },
  {
    id: "3_55",
    question: "__________ : The lowest point of a flue within a chimney. (NFPA 211 3.3.34)",
    options: ["Smoke Shelf", "Throat", "Chimney Flue Base", "Flue Collar"],
    answer: "Chimney Flue Base"
  },
  {
    id: "3_56",
    question: "__________ : An opening or hole in a chimney, usually located near its base, designed to allow access to the flue for purposes of removing ash, creosote, soot, and other extraneous matter that becomes trapped. (NFPA 211 3.3.37)",
    options: ["Ash Dump", "Damper", "Breech", "Cleanout Opening"],
    answer: "Cleanout Opening"
  },
  {
    id: "3_57",
    question: "__________ : The distance between a heat-producing appliance, chimney, chimney connector, vent, vent connector, or plenum and other surfaces. (NFPA 211 3.3.38)",
    options: ["Requirements", "Clearance", "Accessible", "Standard"],
    answer: "Clearance"
  },
  {
    id: "3_58",
    question: "__________ : A device used to dry wet laundry by means of heat derived from the combustion of fuel or from electric heating elements. (NFPA 211 3.3.39)",
    options: ["Air", "Fireplace", "Clothes Dryer", "Furnace"],
    answer: "Clothes Dryer"
  },
  {
    id: "3_59",
    question: "__________ : A factory-built, mass produced dryer, primarily used in a family living environment. It might or might not be coin-operated for public use and usually is the smallest unit both physically and in function. (NFPA 211 3.3.39.1)",
    options: ["Boiler", "Fireplace", "Type 1 Clothes Dryer", "Type 2 Clothes Dryer"],
    answer: "Type 1 Clothes Dryer"
  },
  {
    id: "3_60",
    question: "__________ : A factory-built, mass produced dryer used in a commercial business. It might or might not be operated by the public or a hired attendant. It might or might not be coin-operated and is not designed for use in an individual family living environment. It can be small, medium, or large in size. (NFPA 211 3.3.39.2)",
    options: ["Boiler", "Fireplace", "Type 1 Clothes Dryer", "Type 2 Clothes Dryer"],
    answer: "Type 2 Clothes Dryer"
  },
  {
    id: "3_61",
    question: "__________ : A chemical process of oxidation that occurs at a rate fast enough to produce heat and usually light in the form of either a flow or flame. (NFPA 211 3.3.44)",
    options: ["Pyrolysis", "Drying", "Combustion", "Char"],
    answer: "Combustion"
  },
  {
    id: "3_62",
    question: "__________ : Constituents resulting from the combustion of a fuel with oxygen of the air, including the inert but excluding excess air. (NFPA 211 3.3.46)",
    options: ["Combustion", "Combustion Products", "Pressure", "Refractory Products"],
    answer: "Combustion Products"
  },
  {
    id: "3_63",
    question: "__________ : Not capable of being exposed for inspection, maintenance, or repair without damage to the chimney, building structure, or finished surfaces; without removal of permanently attached parts of the building; or without special tools. (NFPA 211 3.3.48)",
    options: ["Readily Accessible", "Accessible", "Concealed (Inaccessible)", "Barely Accessible"],
    answer: "Concealed (Inaccessible)"
  },
  {
    id: "3_64",
    question: "__________ : The pipe that connects a fuel-burning appliance to a chimney. (NFPA 211 3.3.49.1)",
    options: ["Flue", "Liner", "Chimney Connector", "Vent Connector"],
    answer: "Chimney Connector"
  },
  {
    id: "3_65",
    question: "__________ : The pipe that connects a fuel-burning appliance to a gas vent or Type L vent. (NFPA 211 3.3.49.2)",
    options: ["Flue", "Liner", "Chimney Connector", "Vent Connector"],
    answer: "Vent Connector"
  },
  {
    id: "3_66",
    question: "__________ : Units of masonry projecting from or projecting upward and outward from the face of a wall or chimney in courses to form a support or ledge for a beam, rafter, or other member. (NFPA 211 3.3.50)",
    options: ["Corbel", "Supporting Brick", "Lintel", "Structural Wall"],
    answer: "Corbel"
  },
  {
    id: "3_67",
    question: "__________ : A sloped covering for the top of a masonry chimney that is designed to shed water away from the flue liner and the chimney and to allow expansion and movement of the flue liner. (NFPA 211 3.3.52)",
    options: ["Chimney Cap", "Waterproofing Application", "Crown", "Spall"],
    answer: "Crown"
  },
  {
    id: "3_68",
    question: "__________ : A valve or plate for controlling draft or the flow of gases, including air. (NFPA 211 3.3.53)",
    options: ["Draft Hood", "Damper", "Catalytic Converter", "Baffle Board"],
    answer: "Damper"
  },
  {
    id: "3_69",
    question: "__________ : A damper operated by an automatic control. (NFPA 211 3.3.53.1)",
    options: ["Manually Operated Damper", "Automatically Operated Damper", "Flue Gas Damper", "Throat"],
    answer: "Automatically Operated Damper"
  },
  {
    id: "3_70",
    question: "__________ : A damper located on the downstream side of the combustion chamber of a fuel-burning appliance, usually in a flue passage of the appliance or in the chimney or vent connector. (NFPA 211 3.3.53.2)",
    options: ["Manually Operated Damper", "Automatically Operated Damper", "Flue Gas Damper", "Throat"],
    answer: "Flue Gas Damper"
  },
  {
    id: "3_71",
    question: "__________ : An adjustable damper manually set and locked in the desired position. (NFPA 211 3.3.53.3)",
    options: ["Manually Operated Damper", "Automatically Operated Damper", "Flue Gas Damper", "Throat"],
    answer: "Manually Operated Damper"
  },
  {
    id: "3_72",
    question: "__________ : A pressure difference that causes gases or air to flow through a chimney, vent, flue, or appliance. (NFPA 211 3.3.57)",
    options: ["Flow", "Barometric Damper", "Draft", "Thermodynamics"],
    answer: "Draft"
  },
  {
    id: "3_73",
    question: "__________ : Draft produced by a fan or an air or steam jet. (NFPA 211 3.3.57.1)",
    options: ["Mechanical Flow", "Mechanical Draft", "Natural Draft", "Natural Flow"],
    answer: "Mechanical Draft"
  },
  {
    id: "3_74",
    question: "__________ : Draft produced by the difference in the weight of a column of flue gases within a chimney or vent system and a corresponding column of air of equal dimension outside the chimney or venting system. (NFPA 211 3.3.57.2)",
    options: ["Mechanical Flow", "Mechanical Draft", "Natural Draft", "Natural Flow"],
    answer: "Natural Draft"
  },
  {
    id: "3_75",
    question: "__________ : A nonadjustable device built into an appliance, or made a part of the vent connector from an appliance, that is designed to (1) provide for the ready escape of the flue gases from the appliance in the event of no draft, back-draft, or stoppage beyond the draft hood, (2) prevent a back-draft from entering the appliance, and (3) neutralize the effect of stack action of the chimney or gas vent upon the operation of the appliance. (NFPA 211 3.3.58)",
    options: ["Draft Hood", "Flue Collar", "Chimney Cap", "Top Mount Damper"],
    answer: "Draft Hood"
  },
  {
    id: "3_76",
    question: "__________ : A blower or exhauster assembly comprising blades or runners and housings or casings. (NFPA 211 3.3.67)",
    options: ["Draft", "Fan", "Flow", "Heat Exchanger"],
    answer: "Fan"
  },
  {
    id: "3_77",
    question: "__________ : A hearth, fire chamber, or similarly prepared area and a chimney. (NFPA 211 3.3.69)",
    options: ["Insert", "Stove", "Fireplace", "Boiler"],
    answer: "Fireplace"
  },
  {
    id: "3_78",
    question: "__________ : A fireplace composed of listed, factory-built components assembled in accordance with the terms of the listing. (NFPA 211 3.3.69.1)",
    options: ["Factory-Built Chimney", "Factory-Built Fireplace", "Masonry Fireplace", "Masonry Chimney"],
    answer: "Factory-Built Fireplace"
  },
  {
    id: "3_79",
    question: "__________ : A hearth and fire chamber of solid masonry units, such as bricks, stones, listed masonry units, or reinforced concrete, provided with a suitable chimney. (NFPA 211 3.3.69.2)",
    options: ["Factory-Built Chimney", "Factory-Built Fireplace", "Masonry Fireplace", "Masonry Chimney"],
    answer: "Masonry Fireplace"
  },
  {
    id: "3_80",
    question: "__________ : A factory-built, field-installed product consisting of a firebox assembly designed to be installed within or partially within the fire chamber of a fireplace that uses the fireplace flue to vent the products of combustion. (NFPA 211 3.3.70)",
    options: ["Fireplace Insert", "Factory-Built Fireplace", "Masonry Fireplace", "Fireplace Stove"],
    answer: "Fireplace Insert"
  },
  {
    id: "3_81",
    question: "__________ : A freestanding, chimney-connected, solid fuel-burning appliance that is designed to be operated with the fire chamber either open or closed. (NFPA 211 3.3.71)",
    options: ["Fireplace Insert", "Factory-Built Fireplace", "Masonry Fireplace", "Fireplace Stove"],
    answer: "Fireplace Stove"
  },
  {
    id: "3_82",
    question: "__________ : A chimney-connected, solid fuel-burning room heater that is designed to be operated with the fire chamber either open or closed. (NFPA 211 3.3.71)",
    options: ["Fireplace Insert", "Factory-Built Fireplace", "Masonry Fireplace", "Combination Room Heater/Fireplace Stove"],
    answer: "Combination Room Heater/Fireplace Stove"
  },
  {
    id: "3_83",
    question: "__________ : A noncombustible surfacing applied to the floor area underneath and extending in front, to the sides, and to the rear of a heat-producing appliance. (NFPA 211 3.3.73)",
    options: ["Clearance", "Firebox", "Floor Protector", "Hearth"],
    answer: "Floor Protector"
  },
  {
    id: "3_84",
    question: "__________ : The general term for a passage through which gases are conveyed from the combustion chamber to the outer air. (NFPA 211 3.3.74)",
    options: ["Connector", "Breech", "Flue", "Chimney"],
    answer: "Flue"
  },
  {
    id: "3_85",
    question: "__________ : The flue passage within an appliance. (NFPA 211 3.3.74.1)",
    options: ["Flue Collar", "Appliance Flue", "Chimney Flue", "Dilution Flue"],
    answer: "Appliance Flue"
  },
  {
    id: "3_86",
    question: "__________ : The passage in a chimney for conveying the flue gases to the outside atmosphere. (NFPA 211 3.3.74.2)",
    options: ["Flue Collar", "Appliance Flue", "Chimney Flue", "Dilution Flue"],
    answer: "Chimney Flue"
  },
  {
    id: "3_87",
    question: "__________ : A passage designed to effect the dilution of flue gases with air before discharge from an appliance. (NFPA 211 3.3.74.3)",
    options: ["Flue Collar", "Appliance Flue", "Chimney Flue", "Dilution Flue"],
    answer: "Dilution Flue"
  },
  {
    id: "3_88",
    question: "__________ : That portion of an appliance designed for attachment of a chimney or vent connector or a draft hood. (NFPA 211 3.3.75)",
    options: ["Flue Collar", "Flue", "Connector", "Thimble"],
    answer: "Flue Collar"
  },
  {
    id: "3_89",
    question: "__________ : A material used to produce heat or power by burning. (NFPA 211 3.3.79)",
    options: ["Heating Appliance", "Air", "Fuel", "Heat"],
    answer: "Fuel"
  },
  {
    id: "3_90",
    question: "__________ : A solid processed fuel of specified size and composition capable of being fed to the appliance combustion system at a controlled rate. (NFPA 211 3.3.79.1)",
    options: ["Natural Gas", "Seasoned Wood", "Pellet Fuel", "Gasoline"],
    answer: "Pellet Fuel"
  },
  {
    id: "3_91",
    question: "__________ : Wood, coal, and other similar organic materials and any combination of them. (NFPA 211 3.3.79.2)",
    options: ["Pellet Fuel", "Solid Fuel", "Combustion", "BTU"],
    answer: "Solid Fuel"
  },
  {
    id: "3_92",
    question: "__________ : A forced-air-type furnace designed specifically for installation in an attic or in a space with low headroom that is normally occupied. (NFPA 211 3.3.80.1)",
    options: ["Central Warm-Air, Forced-Air, Attic-Type Furnace", "Central Warm-Air, Forced-Air, Downflow-Type Furnace", "Central Warm-Air, Forced-Air, Upflow-Type Furnace", "Central Warm-Air, Forced-Air, Horizontal-Type Furnace"],
    answer: "Central Warm-Air, Forced-Air, Attic-Type Furnace"
  },
  {
    id: "3_93",
    question: "__________ : A forced-air-type furnace designed with airflow essentially in a vertical path, discharging air at or near the bottom of the furnace. (NFPA 211 3.3.80.2)",
    options: ["Central Warm-Air, Forced-Air, Attic-Type Furnace", "Central Warm-Air, Forced-Air, Downflow-Type Furnace", "Central Warm-Air, Forced-Air, Upflow-Type Furnace", "Central Warm-Air, Forced-Air, Horizontal-Type Furnace"],
    answer: "Central Warm-Air, Forced-Air, Downflow-Type Furnace"
  },
  {
    id: "3_94",
    question: "__________ : A forced-air-type furnace designed with airflow through the furnace, essentially in a horizontal path. (NFPA 211 3.3.80.3)",
    options: ["Central Warm-Air, Forced-Air, Attic-Type Furnace", "Central Warm-Air, Forced-Air, Downflow-Type Furnace", "Central Warm-Air, Forced-Air, Upflow-Type Furnace", "Central Warm-Air, Forced-Air, Horizontal-Type Furnace"],
    answer: "Central Warm-Air, Forced-Air, Horizontal-Type Furnace"
  },
  {
    id: "3_95",
    question: "__________ : A forced-air-type furnace designed with airflow essentially in a vertical path, discharging at air at or near the top of the furnace. (NFPA 211 3.3.80.4)",
    options: ["Central Warm-Air, Forced-Air, Attic-Type Furnace", "Central Warm-Air, Forced-Air, Downflow-Type Furnace", "Central Warm-Air, Forced-Air, Upflow-Type Furnace", "Central Warm-Air, Forced-Air, Horizontal-Type Furnace"],
    answer: "Central Warm-Air, Forced-Air, Upflow-Type Furnace"
  },
  {
    id: "3_96",
    question: "__________ : A central furnace equipped with a blower that provides the primary means for the circulation of air. (NFPA 211 3.3.80.5)",
    options: ["Central Warm-Air, Forced-Air-Type Furnace", "Duct Furnace", "Floor Furnace", "Combination-Fuel Furnace"],
    answer: "Central Warm-Air, Forced-Air-Type Furnace"
  },
  {
    id: "3_97",
    question: "__________ : A self-contained indirect-fired or electrically heated appliance designed to supply heated air through ducts to spaces remote from or adjacent to the appliance location. (NFPA 211 3.3.80.6)",
    options: ["Central Warm-Air Furnace", "Duct Furnace", "Floor Furnace", "Combination-Fuel Furnace"],
    answer: "Central Warm-Air Furnace"
  },
  {
    id: "3_98",
    question: "__________ : A central furnace depending primarily on circulation of air by gravity. (NFPA 211 3.3.80.7)",
    options: ["Central Warm-Air, Forced-Air-Type Furnace", "Duct Furnace", "Floor Furnace", "Central Warm-Air, Gravity-Type Furnace"],
    answer: "Central Warm-Air, Gravity-Type Furnace"
  },
  {
    id: "3_99",
    question: "__________ : A central furnace equipped with a booster fan that does not materially restrict free circulation of air by gravity flow when such a fan is not in operation. (NFPA 211 3.3.80.8)",
    options: ["Central Warm-Air, Forced-Air-Type Furnace", "Central Warm-Air, Gravity-Type Furnace with Integral Fan", "Floor Furnace", "Central Warm-Air, Gravity-Type Furnace with Booster Fan"],
    answer: "Central Warm-Air, Gravity-Type Furnace with Booster Fan"
  },
  {
    id: "3_100",
    question: "__________ : A central furnace equipped with a fan as an integral part of its construction and operable on gravity systems only. The fan is used to overcome the internal resistance to airflow. (NFPA 211 3.3.80.9)",
    options: ["Central Warm-Air, Forced-Air-Type Furnace", "Central Warm-Air, Gravity-Type Furnace with Integral Fan", "Floor Furnace", "Central Warm-Air, Gravity-Type Furnace with Booster Fan"],
    answer: "Central Warm-Air, Gravity-Type Furnace with Integral Fan"
  },
  {
    id: "3_101",
    question: "__________ : A single furnace unit designed to burn more than one type of fuel (gas, oil, or solid), either separately or simultaneously, using either separate or common combustion chambers and flues. (NFPA 211 3.3.80.10)",
    options: ["Central Warm-Air Furnace", "Duct Furnace", "Floor Furnace", "Combination-Fuel Furnace"],
    answer: "Combination-Fuel Furnace"
  },
  {
    id: "3_102",
    question: "__________ : A central furnace designed for installation in a duct of an air distribution system to supply warm air for heating and that depends on a blower not furnished as part of the furnace for air circulation. (NFPA 211 3.3.80.11)",
    options: ["Central Warm-Air Furnace", "Duct Furnace", "Floor Furnace", "Combination-Fuel Furnace"],
    answer: "Duct Furnace"
  },
  {
    id: "3_103",
    question: "__________ : A self-contained indirect-fired or electrically heated furnace designed to be suspended from the floor of the space to be heated. A fuel-burning floor furnace is designed to take air for combustion from outside the space being heated and is provided with means for observing the flame and lighting the appliance from such space. (NFPA 211 3.3.80.12)",
    options: ["Central Warm-Air Furnace", "Duct Furnace", "Floor Furnace", "Combination-Fuel Furnace"],
    answer: "Floor Furnace"
  },
  {
    id: "3_104",
    question: "__________ : A floor furnace equipped with a blower that provides the primary means for circulation of air. (NFPA 211 3.3.80.12.1)",
    options: ["Central Warm-Air Furnace", "Fan-Type Floor Furnace", "Gravity-Type Floor Furnace", "Combination-Fuel Furnace"],
    answer: "Fan-Type Floor Furnace"
  },
  {
    id: "3_105",
    question: "__________ : A floor furnace depending primarily on circulation of air by gravity. This classification also includes floor furnaces equipped with booster-type fans that do not materially restrict free circulation of air by gravity flow when such fans are not in operation. (NFPA 211 3.3.80.12.2)",
    options: ["Central Warm-Air Furnace", "Fan-Type Floor Furnace", "Gravity-Type Floor Furnace", "Combination-Fuel Furnace"],
    answer: "Gravity-Type Floor Furnace"
  },
  {
    id: "3_106",
    question: "__________ : A furnace designed to burn one type of fuel (gas, oil, or solid) that is intended for supplementing a central warm-air furnace burning another type of fuel (gas, oil, or solid) by means of a common warm air supply plenum. (NFPA 211 3.3.80.13)",
    options: ["Central Warm-Air Furnace", "Supplementary Furnace", "Gravity-Type Floor Furnace", "Combination-Fuel Furnace"],
    answer: "Supplementary Furnace"
  },
  {
    id: "3_107",
    question: "How many categories are there for Vented Gas Appliances? (NFPA 211 3.3.81)",
    options: ["1", "2", "3", "4"],
    answer: "4"
  },
  {
    id: "3_108",
    question: "__________ : This Vented Gas Appliance Category is an appliance that operates with a non-positive vent static pressure and with a vent gas temperature that avoids excessive condensate production in the vent. (NFPA 211 3.3.81)",
    options: ["Category 1", "Category 2", "Category 3", "Category 4"],
    answer: "Category 1"
  },
  {
    id: "3_109",
    question: "__________ : This Vented Gas Appliance Category is an appliance that operates with a non-positive vent static pressure and with a vent gas temperature that may cause excessive condensate production in the vent. (NFPA 211 3.3.81)",
    options: ["Category 1", "Category 2", "Category 3", "Category 4"],
    answer: "Category 2"
  },
  {
    id: "3_110",
    question: "__________ : This Vented Gas Appliance Category is an appliance that operates with a positive vent static pressure and with a vent gas temperature that avoids excessive condensate production in the vent. (NFPA 211 3.3.81)",
    options: ["Category 1", "Category 2", "Category 3", "Category 4"],
    answer: "Category 3"
  },
  {
    id: "3_111",
    question: "__________ : This Vented Gas Appliance Category is an appliance that operates with a positive vent static pressure and with a vent gas temperature that may cause excessive condensate production in the vent. (NFPA 211 3.3.81)",
    options: ["Category 1", "Category 2", "Category 3", "Category 4"],
    answer: "Category 4"
  },
  {
    id: "3_112",
    question: "__________ : Combustion products from fuel-burning appliances along with excess air. (NFPA 211 3.3.83.1)",
    options: ["Flue Gases", "Vent Gases", "Heat", "Creosote"],
    answer: "Flue Gases"
  },
  {
    id: "3_113",
    question: "__________ : Products of combustion from fuel-burning appliances along with excess air, plus any dilution air in the venting system above a draft hood or draft regulator. (NFPA 211 3.3.83.2)",
    options: ["Flue Gases", "Vent Gases", "Heat", "Creosote"],
    answer: "Vent Gases"
  },
  {
    id: "3_114",
    question: "__________ : Where referring to chimneys, a beam set at right angles to floor or roof joists to provide support and framing around the opening. (NFPA 211 3.3.85)",
    options: ["Hearth", "Header", "Cripple Studs", "Mantel"],
    answer: "Header"
  },
  {
    id: "3_115",
    question: "__________ : The floor area within the fire chamber of a fireplace or a fireplace stove. This is the general term, not Inner _______ / _______ Extension. (NFPA 211 3.3.86)",
    options: ["Hearth", "Hearth Extension", "Firebrick", "Firebox"],
    answer: "Hearth"
  },
  {
    id: "3_116",
    question: "__________ : The noncombustible surfacing applied to the floor area extending to front of and at the sides of the hearth opening of a fireplace or a fireplace stove; also where applied to the floor area beneath a fireplace stove or beneath an elevated overhanging fireplace hearth. (NFPA 211 3.3.87)",
    options: ["Hearth", "Hearth Extension", "Firebrick", "Firebox"],
    answer: "Hearth Extension"
  },
  {
    id: "3_117",
    question: "__________ : A chamber in which heat resulting directly from the combustion of fuel, or heat from a medium such as air, water, or steam, is transferred through the walls of the chamber to air passing through the exchanger; or a chamber in which heat from electric resistors is transferred to the air. (NFPA 211 3.3.88)",
    options: ["Jacket", "Heat Exchanger", "Smoke Chamber", "Firebox"],
    answer: "Heat Exchanger"
  },
  {
    id: "3_118",
    question: "__________ : A vented heating system of predominantly masonry construction having a mass of at least 1760 lb excluding the chimney and masonry heater base. (NFPA 211 3.3.89.1)",
    options: ["Masonry Heater", "Room Heater", "Unit Heater", "Radiant Room Heater"],
    answer: "Masonry Heater"
  },
  {
    id: "3_119",
    question: "__________ : A heating appliance intended for installation in the space being heated and not intended for duct connection. (NFPA 211 3.3.89.2)",
    options: ["Masonry Heater", "Room Heater", "Unit Heater", "Water Heater"],
    answer: "Room Heater"
  },
  {
    id: "3_120",
    question: "__________ : A room heater with an outer jacket surrounding the heat exchanger, arranged with openings at top and bottom so that air circulates between the heat exchanger and the outer jacket. Room heaters that have openings in an outer jacket to allow some direct radiation from the heat exchanger are classified as a radiant type. (NFPA 211 3.3.89.2.1)",
    options: ["Masonry Heater", "Circulating Room Heater", "Unit Heater", "Radiant Room Heater"],
    answer: "Circulating Room Heater"
  },
  {
    id: "3_121",
    question: "__________ : A room heater designed to transfer heat primarily by direct radiation. (NFPA 211 3.3.89.2.2)",
    options: ["Solid Fuel Room Heater", "Circulating Room Heater", "Unit Heater", "Radiant Room Heater"],
    answer: "Radiant Room Heater"
  },
  {
    id: "3_122",
    question: "__________ : A chimney-connected, solid-fuel burning room heater that is designed to be operated with the fire chamber closed. (NFPA 211 3.3.89.2.3)",
    options: ["Solid Fuel Room Heater", "Circulating Room Heater", "Unit Heater", "Radiant Room Heater"],
    answer: "Solid Fuel Room Heater"
  },
  {
    id: "3_123",
    question: "__________ : A self-contained heating appliance that is intended for the heating of the space in which it is installed. This heater can be an indirect-fired fuel-burning appliance or might utilize steam, hot water, or electricity. (NFPA 211 3.3.89.3)",
    options: ["Solid Fuel Room Heater", "Water Heater", "Unit Heater", "Radiant Room Heater"],
    answer: "Unit Heater"
  },
  {
    id: "3_124",
    question: "__________ : A fuel-burning appliance for heating water to a temperature not more than 200°F. (NFPA 211 3.3.89.4)",
    options: ["Solid Fuel Room Heater", "Water Heater", "Unit Heater", "Radiant Room Heater"],
    answer: "Water Heater"
  },
  {
    id: "3_125",
    question: "__________ : An appliance or combustion chamber for the reduction, by burning, of rubbish, garbage, and other wastes. (NFPA 211 3.3.92)",
    options: ["Open Fireplace", "Heat Exchanger", "Incinerator", "Furnace"],
    answer: "Incinerator"
  },
  {
    id: "3_126",
    question: "__________ : An incinerator designed specifically to be fed refuse from one or more floors above the incinerator directly into the incinerator by a separate chute constructed with a positive means to avoid penetration by smoke or fumes and connected directly over the primary combustion chamber. The incinerator is built with a primary and a secondary combustion chamber and a settling chamber. It can include a flue gas washer or scrubber. A separate chimney serves to convey the combustion gases to the outdoors. This class of incinerator is suitable for gases to the outdoors. This class of incinerator is suitable for Type 1 and Type 2 wastes. It generally is used in residential and institutional buildings, including apartments, clubs, dormitories, churches, schools, and other occupancies where Type 1 and Type 2 wastes are to be incinerated. (NFPA 211 3.3.92.1)",
    options: ["Chute-Fed Incinerator (Class IIA)", "Commercial-Industrial-Type Incinerator (Classes III, IV, V, VI, and VII)", "Flue-Fed Incinerator (Class II)", "Residential-Type Incinerator"],
    answer: "Chute-Fed Incinerator (Class IIA)"
  },
  {
    id: "3_127",
    question: "__________ : An incinerator having a charging capacity in excess of 5ft³ and suitable for a variety of wastes as follows (1) Class III -- Waste Type 0, Type 1, or Type 2; (2) Class IV -- Waste Type 3; (3) Class V -- Waste Types 0-4 (municipal incinerators); (4) Class VI -- Waste Type 4; (5) Class VII -- Waste Type 5 and 6. (NFPA 211 3.3.92.2)",
    options: ["Chute-Fed Incinerator (Class IIA)", "Commercial-Industrial-Type Incinerator (Classes III, IV, V, VI, and VII)", "Flue-Fed Incinerator (Class II)", "Residential-Type Incinerator"],
    answer: "Commercial-Industrial-Type Incinerator (Classes III, IV, V, VI, and VII)"
  },
  {
    id: "3_128",
    question: "__________ : An incinerator served by a single chimney flue that serves also as the charging chute, where refuse is fed directly to the incinerator through this chimney flue from one or more floors above the incinerator. This class of incinerator is suitable for Type 1 and Type 2 waste materials and garbage incidental to residential occupancy in a single-family and multifamily buildings. This class of incinerator is generally used in residential and institutional buildings including apartments, clubs, dormitories, churches, schools, and other occupancies where Type 1 and Type 2 wastes are to be incinerated. (NFPA 211 3.3.92.3)",
    options: ["Chute-Fed Incinerator (Class IIA)", "Commercial-Industrial-Type Incinerator (Classes III, IV, V, VI, and VII)", "Flue-Fed Incinerator (Class II)", "Residential-Type Incinerator"],
    answer: "Flue-Fed Incinerator (Class II)"
  },
  {
    id: "3_129",
    question: "__________ : An incinerator for the burning of ordinary combustible waste material and garbage (Type 2 waste) incidental to residential occupancy and having a firebox or charging compartment not greater than 5ft³ in capacity. Residential-type incinerators can be self-contained, factory-built units that do not necessitate field construction, or can be of a built in type designed to be encased in masonry or installed in a masonry wall or chimney. (NFPA 211 3.3.92.4)",
    options: ["Chute-Fed Incinerator (Class IIA)", "Commercial-Industrial-Type Incinerator (Classes III, IV, V, VI, and VII)", "Flue-Fed Incinerator (Class II)", "Residential-Type Incinerator"],
    answer: "Residential-Type Incinerator"
  },
  {
    id: "3_130",
    question: "__________ : A shelf or facing ornament above a fireplace opening. (NFPA 211 3.3.94)",
    options: ["Trim", "Stone Facing", "Smoke Shelf", "Mantel"],
    answer: "Mantel"
  },
  {
    id: "3_131",
    question: "__________ : The person or persons, company, firm, corporation, partnership, or other organization responsible for turning raw materials or components into a finished product. (NFPA 211 3.3.96)",
    options: ["Qualified Agency", "Manufacturer", "AHJ", "Installer"],
    answer: "Manufacturer"
  },
  {
    id: "3_132",
    question: "__________ : The horizontal, noncombustible member, usually of masonry or steel, spanning the opening of a masonry fireplace to support the load above. (NFPA 211 3.3.99)",
    options: ["Corbelling", "Smoke Shelf", "Masonry Fireplace Lintel", "Header"],
    answer: "Masonry Fireplace Lintel"
  },
  {
    id: "3_133",
    question: "__________ : A material that, in the form in which it is used and under the conditions anticipated, will ignite and burn; a material that does not meet the definition of noncombustible or limited-combustible. (NFPA 211 3.3.99)",
    options: ["Refractory", "Combustible Material", "Creosote Buster", "Masonry"],
    answer: "Combustible Material"
  },
  {
    id: "3_134",
    question: "__________ : Any individual, firm, corporation, or company that, either in person or through a representative, is engaged in and is responsible for the connection, venting, installation, inspection, repair, or servicing of heat-producing appliances and who is experienced in such work, is familiar with all precautions required, and has complied with all the requirements of the AHJ. (NFPA 211 3.3.112)",
    options: ["AHJ", "Qualified Agency", "Chimney Business", "Manufacturer"],
    answer: "Qualified Agency"
  },
  {
    id: "3_135",
    question: "__________ : A factory-built assembly for conveying flue gases through a roof and that includes a flue gas passageway, an insulating means, flashing, and a cap. (NFPA 211 3.3.117)",
    options: ["Chase", "Roof Jack", "Stainless Steel Liner", "Cricket"],
    answer: "Roof Jack"
  },
  {
    id: "3_136",
    question: "__________ : The transitional area from the damper opening to the beginning of the flue liner in a fireplace system. (NFPA 211 3.3.119)",
    options: ["Throat", "Smoke Shelf", "Flue Collar", "Smoke Chamber"],
    answer: "Smoke Chamber"
  },
  {
    id: "3_137",
    question: "__________ : A procedure for ascertaining the tightness of a chimney and for detecting any cracks in a masonry chimney flue or deterioration or breaks in the integrity of a metal chimney flue, and that involves igniting a smoke bomb or building a smoky fire in a fireplace or solid fuel-burning appliance, covering the chimney termination, and checking for smoke escapage through the chimney walls. (NFPA 211 3.3.120)",
    options: ["Level 2 Inspection", "Smoke Test", "Video Inspection", "Level 3 Inspection"],
    answer: "Smoke Test"
  },
  {
    id: "3_138",
    question: "__________ : A bonded assembly of stones or solid masonry units. (NFPA 211 3.3.124)",
    options: ["Bond", "Installed Unit", "Solid Masonry Construction", "Fireplace Insert"],
    answer: "Solid Masonry Construction"
  },
  {
    id: "3_139",
    question: "__________ : A masonry unit whose net cross-sectional area in every plane parallel to the bearing surface is 75 percent or more of its gross cross-sectional area measured in the same plane. (NFPA 211 3.3.125)",
    options: ["Free Standing Wood Stove", "Solid Masonry Unit", "Solid Masonry Construction", "Fireplace Insert"],
    answer: "Solid Masonry Unit"
  },
  {
    id: "3_140",
    question: "__________ : Screening material or a screening device attached to a chimney termination to prevent the passage of sparks and brands to the outside atmosphere. (NFPA 211 3.3.126)",
    options: ["Cap", "Spark Arrestors", "Mesh", "Damper"],
    answer: "Spark Arrestors"
  },
  {
    id: "3_141",
    question: "__________ : A unit consisting of a steel firebox and an air chamber adjacent to the sides and rear of the firebox, used to construct a masonry fireplace. the unit usually has ducts to circulate air to and heated air from the air chamber to the living space. (NFPA 211 3.3.129)",
    options: ["Steel Fireplace Unit", "Free Standing Wood Stove", "Unit with Gas Logs", "Lintel"],
    answer: "Steel Fireplace Unit"
  },
  {
    id: "3_142",
    question: "__________ : A system that has been sized and configured in accordance with approved engineering methods. (NFPA 211 3.3.132.1)",
    options: ["Direct Vent Appliance", "Engineered Venting or Chimney System", "Roof Jack", "Fire Blocking"],
    answer: "Engineered Venting or Chimney System"
  },
  {
    id: "3_143",
    question: "__________ : A continuous, open passageway from the flue collar or draft hood of a fuel-burning appliance to the outside atmosphere for the purpose of removing flue gases. (NFPA 211 3.3.132.2)",
    options: ["Venting System (Flue Gases)", "Category I Gas Appliance", "Stainless Steel Liner", "Furnace"],
    answer: "Venting System (Flue Gases)"
  },
  {
    id: "3_144",
    question: "__________ : A fixed or removable ring, tube, or lining usually located in the hole where the chimney connector or vent connector passes through a wall or enters a chimney or vent. (NFPA 211 3.3.133)",
    options: ["Breech", "Thimble", "Flue", "Flue Collar"],
    answer: "Thimble"
  },
  {
    id: "3_145",
    question: "__________ : Where referring to chimneys, the longer floor or roof framing member around a rectangular opening into which the end of a header is joined. (NFPA 211 3.3.134)",
    options: ["Lintel", "Cricket", "Trimmer", "Cripple Stud"],
    answer: "Trimmer"
  },
  {
    id: "3_146",
    question: "__________ : A flue gas-conveying system intended for use only with certain gas, liquid, or pellet fuel-fired appliances that do not produce flue gas outlet temperatures higher than a value specified in the listing vent standards. (NFPA 211 3.3.143)",
    options: ["Wash", "Draft Hood", "Vent", "Flow"],
    answer: "Vent"
  },
  {
    id: "3_147",
    question: "__________ : A passageway composed of listed factory-built components assembled in accordance with the manufacturer's installation instructions for conveying vent gases from appliances or their vent connectors to the outdoors. (NFPA 211 3.3.143.1)",
    options: ["Pellet Vent", "Gas Vent", "Type L Vent", "Smokestack"],
    answer: "Gas Vent"
  },
  {
    id: "3_148",
    question: "__________ : A gas vent for venting listed Category II, III, and IV gas appliances. (NFPA 211 3.3.143.1.1)",
    options: ["Type B Gas Vent", "Type BW Gas Vent", "Type L Vent", "Special Gas Vent"],
    answer: "Special Gas Vent"
  },
  {
    id: "3_149",
    question: "__________ : A vent for venting listed gas appliances with draft hoods and other category I appliances listed for use with type B gas vents. (NFPA 211 3.3.143.1.2)",
    options: ["Type B Gas Vent", "Type BW Gas Vent", "Type L Vent", "Special Gas Vent"],
    answer: "Type B Gas Vent"
  },
  {
    id: "3_150",
    question: "__________ : A vertical or nearly vertical gas vent for venting listed gas-fired vented wall furnaces. (NFPA 211 3.3.143.1.3)",
    options: ["Type B Gas Vent", "Type BW Gas Vent", "Type L Vent", "Special Gas Vent"],
    answer: "Type BW Gas Vent"
  },
  {
    id: "3_151",
    question: "__________ : A venting system composed of listed, factory-built components assembled in accordance with the manufacturer's instructions for conveying flue gases from a listed pellet fuel-burning appliance to the outside atmosphere. (NFPA 211 3.3.143.2)",
    options: ["Type B Gas Vent", "Type BW Gas Vent", "Type L Vent", "Pellet Vent"],
    answer: "Pellet Vent"
  },
  {
    id: "3_152",
    question: "__________ : A vertical or nearly vertical vent composed of listed factory-built components assembled in accordance with the terms of a listing for conveying flue gases from oil and gas appliances or their vent connectors to the outside atmosphere. (NFPA 211 3.3.143.3)",
    options: ["Type B Gas Vent", "Type BW Gas Vent", "Type L Vent", "Pellet Vent"],
    answer: "Type L Vent"
  },
  {
    id: "3_153",
    question: "__________ : Removal of combustion products as well as noxious or toxic fumes to the outside atmosphere. (NFPA 211 3.3.148)",
    options: ["Annual Cleaning", "Venting", "Draft", "Standard"],
    answer: "Venting"
  },
  {
    id: "3_154",
    question: "__________ : Noncombustible surfacing applied to a wall area for the purpose of reducing the clearance between the wall and a heat-producing appliance. (NFPA 211 3.3.150)",
    options: ["Hearth", "Floor Protector", "Fire Stop", "Wall Protector (Shield)"],
    answer: "Wall Protector (Shield)"
  },
  {
    id: "3_155",
    question: "__________ : A slight slope or beveled edge on the top surface of a chimney designed to shed water away from the flue liner; also called a 'Splay'. (NFPA 211 3.3.151)",
    options: ["Cap", "Wash", "Wythe", "Corbel"],
    answer: "Wash"
  },
  {
    id: "3_156",
    question: "__________ : Where referring to masonry chimneys, a course, a thickness, or a continuous vertical section of masonry separating flues in a chimney. (NFPA 211 3.3.153)",
    options: ["Cap", "Crown", "Wythe", "Corbel"],
    answer: "Wythe"
  },
];

if (!window.quizRegistry) window.quizRegistry = {};
window.quizRegistry['Chapter 3: Definitions'] = nfpa211Chapter3QuizData;

